找到标着机顶盒的按钮 奶奶
Find the button that says "cable," Grandma.
[woman speaking indistinctly over phone]
应该是在遥控器的最上方
Should be on the top of the remote.
是的 那个
Yeah, the...
好的 现在 现在 按下标着 电源 的按钮
Okay, now, now... push the "power" button.
Do you see a blue light on the... on the cable box?
你看到机顶盒上出现蓝色的光点了吗
[woman continues speaking indistinctly over phone]
我 我不知道 奶奶 它就是这么工作的
I-I don't know, Grandma. That's just the way it works.
No, you can't have your old remote back.
不 你不能用你的旧遥控器
啊 真是惊险
Whoo! What a rush!
因为它已经在垃圾桶里了 因为我把它扔了
Because it's in the trash, that's why. I threw it out.
More loofahs? Come on, people.
又是丝瓜瓤吗 给点儿力啊
Mama needs a new pair of shoes.
我需要一双新鞋
呃 Edie说她也爱你 想你了
Uh, uh, Edie says she loves and misses you, too.
好的 我今晚就把车还你 我保证
Ye... Okay, I'll have the car back to you tonight, I promise.
I got to go. Okay. Love you. Okay, bye.
我得走了 好 爱你 好 拜拜
[electrical whirring]What the...?
这他...
♪
F
"F."
没有F 你输了
No "F." You lose.
[video game music plays]
Wait. What?
等下 什么
不 那眼睛 嘴 和脸呢
No, what about the-the eyes and the mouth and the face?
There is no face in hangman.
上吊小人没有脸
Bishop.
Bishop
我不掺和
Not getting involved.
Sorry I'm late.
抱歉我来晚了
而且我下一个会也晚了
And I'm already late for my next meeting,
所以我们现在赶紧开始 我好早点走
so let's get started so we can get finished.
大家都看一眼这些文件
Everyone, take a look at these documents.
她是谁
Who is she?
机构律师 从来没带来过好消息
Agency attorney. Never good news.
NCIS不会再继续使用
Effective immediately,
手机信号塔定位跟踪了
NCIS is discontinuing its use
of cell phone tower location tracking.
立即生效
-这样我们就能 -哇 等一下
With this directive, we can...Whoa, whoa, hold on.
你是 你是说我以后再也不能
Are you, are you saying that I can no longer
定位嫌疑人的手机了吗
ping a suspect's cell phone?
除非你有搜查令
Not without a warrant you can't.
嗨 我是Torres探员
Hi. Agent Torres here.
所以 McGee探员 几乎一直都在定位别人的手机
So, uh, Agent McGee, uh, he pings, like, all the time.
就像他的超能力一样
That is like his superpower.
以后不行了 最高法院刚刚裁定这个违法
Not anymore. Supreme Court just ruled it's illegal.
他们做得不对 是不是 McGee
They're wrong. Right, McGee?
实际上 我能理解
Actually, I kind of get it.
有时候隐私比安全需要更重要
Sometimes privacy outweighs the need for security.
不好意思 McGee的意思是 新政策
I'm sorry, what McGee means to say is the new policy
意味着危险的罪犯能逃脱追捕了
means dangerous criminals can get away.
-Vance主任知道这事儿吗 -他还没回来
Does Director Vance know about this?He's on leave.
那Gibbs呢
What about Gibbs?
就是 他怎么了
Yeah, what about him?
海豹突击队成员家外面发生爆炸
Explosion outside a Navy SEAL's house.
两名死者
We have two bodies.
等下 再给我一分钟 先生
Wait, I just need one more minute, sir,
-让我说完 -带上装备
to finish my presentation.Grab your gear.
-带上装备 -带上装备
"Grab your gear.""Grab your gear."
哦 带上装备
Oh, "grab your gear."
这俩傻蛋还好吗
Those two yahoos okay?
我也不确定了
I don't know anymore.
[dogs barking in distance]
我的报纸到底在哪儿
Where's my damn paper?
拜托
Come on.
老天
Geez.
Kayla
Kayla?
你看到报纸了吗
Have you seen the newspaper?
早上好啊爸爸 你来得正是时候
Morning, Dad. You're just in time.
亲爱的 我的报纸
Honey, my newspaper.
我回收了
I recycled it.
这么快 才八点半
Already? It's only 8:30.
就是说你该回去工作了
Which means it's time for you to go back to work.
今天是你回去的第一天
Today's your first day back.
我以为你都洗好澡了
I thought you'd be showered by now.
穿戴整齐了
And dressed.
你咖啡想配点儿什么吗
You want something to go with your coffee?
嗯 我的报纸
Yeah, my newspaper.
你不能轻易跑掉
You are not getting away that easy.
嗯 我注意到了
Yeah, I noticed.
你的胯今天怎么样啊
How's the hip today?
-不咋舒服 -就跟你身上其他部分一样
It's cranky.Like the rest of you.
甜心 谢谢你的早饭
Sweetheart, thank you for breakfast.
很贴心
That was very thoughtful.
但是我今天有物理治疗
But I've got physical therapy today.
所以 明天才能回单位了呗
So, work tomorrow, then?
再看吧
We'll see.
还有这里
And right here.
[camera clicking]
你 你之前从来没见过这辆车吗
You've, uh, you've never seen that vehicle before?
没有 长官 那是谁的车啊
No, sir. Whose is it?
小偷的 邻居们看到了其中一个
Burglars. The neighbors saw one of them
偷了你门廊的包裹
steal a package off your porch.
然后 他们就炸了吗
And then they... exploded?
包裹炸了
The package exploded.
Palmer 我们有什么...
Palmer, what do we...[phone beeping]
收获吗
Got?
嗯
Yeah.
嗯 我们有两名受害者 当场死亡
Well, we got two victims. Death was instantaneous.
死因都是冲击伤
Both died from blast injuries.
你知道今天有包裹送到吗
Were you expecting any deliveries today,
Nicholas上士
Petty Officer Nicholas?
大概吧
Maybe.
我妻子总是在网上买东西
My wife orders stuff online all the time.
根据快递公司的说法
Well, according to the delivery company,
收件人是你
it was addressed to you.
-嘿 嘿 哎 -让我过去
Hey, hey, whoa.Let me through.
我是他妻子
I'm his wife.
-嘿 -Todd
Hey! Todd.
亲爱的 你还好吗
My darling, are you okay?
我很好 我很好
I'm fine. I'm okay.
那是他妻子吗
Is that his wife?
嗯 看起来像是
Uh, yeah. It looks like it.
-她叫Sheba -Sheba
Her name's Sheba.Sheba.
McGee 你认识她吗
McGee, you know her?
嗯 你 你们不认识吗
Yeah. You-you guys don't?
不认识 Bishop 你呢
No. Bishop, do you?
呃 不认识
Uh, no.
我还好
I'm okay.
McGee
McGee.
对不起 老大 她叫Sheba
Sorry, boss. Uh, her name is Sheba.
她是真实战争主妇真人秀的明星之一
She's one of the stars of the show Real Wives of War.
真人秀 你看那个
The reality show? You watch that?
-嗯 Delilah看 -嗯哼
Well, Delilah does.Mm-hmm.
啊哈
Uh-huh.
我的天 你猜怎么的
Oh, my God, you know what?
Nicholas上士一定就是Todd了
Petty Officer Nicholas must be Todd.
这怎么回事儿啊
SHEBA: How could this happen?
Todd 没有出现在真人秀里
Todd-- he's not on the show,
但是她总是谈到他
but she talks about him all the time.
说她自己是世界上最幸运的女人
Says that she is the luckiest woman in the world.
哇哦 Delilah一定很喜欢那个真人秀
Wow. Delilah must, uh, really like that show.
嗯
Yeah.
好吧
Okay.
打扰一下 警官
Excuse me, Officer.
是 抱歉 我是探员
Uh, yes. Sorry, I mean Agent.
我是说 怎么了
I mean, um... what?
请告诉我这不是真的
Please tell me this isn't real.
你说什么
Excuse me?
就真人秀啊 Greg让你来做的吗
It's sweeps. Greg put you up to this?
Greg
Greg.
我的制片人
My producer.
嘿 Torres
Hey, Torres.
呃 不 这是真的
Uh, no, this is real.
有人给你丈夫邮了一个炸弹
Somebody mailed your husband a bomb.
一个炸弹
[clears throat] A bomb?
这说不通啊 你们在说什么
That doesn't make any sense. What are you talking about?
一个炸弹
A bomb?
[Sheba continues talking indistinctly]
I think I know who did this.
我觉得我知道是谁干的
My wife.
我妻子
我们的包裹窃贼是Edie Samples
TORRES: Our package thief is Edie Samples.
A doorbell camera caught her in the act.
门铃相机拍到了她
McGEE: It appears she and boyfriend Walt Fergus
看起来她和她男朋友Walt Fergus
followed the delivery truck
跟在快递卡车后面
and stole all the packages.
然后偷了所有的包裹
They picked the wrong package to poach.
他们偷错了包裹
谁是炸弹真正的目标呢
Who was the bomb's real target?
Todd Nicholas上士
Petty Officer First Class
27岁
Todd Nicholas. 27.
两个月前在海豹突击队训练中毕业的
Graduated from SEAL training two months ago.
成绩优秀
As squared away as they come.
-妻子呢 -Sheba Nicholas
What about his wife?BISHOP: Sheba Nicholas.
25岁 没有孩子 没有犯罪记录 没有工作
25. No kids, no record, no job,
直到她两季前
until she joined the reality show Real Wives of War
加入了真人秀 战争主妇
two seasons ago.
实际上是两季半
McGEE: Actually, it was two and a half.
她在全部的41集里都有出现
She was in all 41 episodes,
如果你把两小节算一集的话
if you count the two-parter as one,
我个人是习惯这么做...的
which I personally like to... do.
继续
Go on.Well, I-I don't know all that much.
我也不是知道那么多
No, it's okay, McGee. I mean, we've already judged you, so...
没 挺好的 我是说 我们已经知道你是什么货色了 所以
哦 好吧
Oh, okay.
这个真人秀是关于四个军嫂的
Well, the show's about four military wives, right?
Charlotte, Tessa, Angela-- Angela's quite the instigator.
Charlotte, Tessa, Angela。Angela挺会煽动人的
Actually, Tess and Char-Char are pretty catty, too.
实际上 Tess和Char-Char也都挺阴险的
-Char-Char -重点在于 Sheba
Char-Char?My point is that Sheba
is the wholesome, virtuous one.
是最健全 最善良的那个
她爱每个人 尤其是她丈夫
She loves everyone, especially her husband.
Last week's episode...
上周那集
We got it. You think she's innocent.
知道了 你觉得她是无辜的
老大 我认识的那个Sheba绝对不会做这样的事的
Boss, the Sheba I know would never do anything like this.
现在我说出来这句话以后 就有点尴尬了
Now that I say that out loud, I feel slightly embarrassed.
Tim 你确实应该觉得尴尬
Hey, Tim... you should be.
Char-Char
GIBBS: "Char-Char."
你能追踪那个包裹吗
Were you able to trace that package?
死胡同 一个叫G. Washington的人寄的
Dead end. It was sent by a "G. Washington"
退回地址是林肯纪念堂
with a return address to the Lincoln Memorial.
轮到你了 你为什么会觉得是你妻子寄的
Your turn. Why do you think your wife sent it?
三天前 Sheba威胁说要杀了我
Three days ago, Sheba threatened to kill me.
为什么
Why?
她觉得我有婚外情
She thinks I'm having an affair.
你有吗
Are you?
我一定要说实话吗 长官
Do I have to tell the truth in here, sir?
那取决于 你喜欢收到炸弹吗
Well, that depends. You like bombs in your mail?
我没有婚外情 但是我告诉她我有
I'm not having an affair. But I told her I was.
好吧
Okay.
我想要脱离我的婚姻
I want out of my marriage.
那个女人已经不是我爱的那个人了
That woman is not the person I fell in love with.
那个真人秀把她变成了一个变态
That show turned her into a total psycho.
问个傻问题 为什么不离婚呢
Silly question: why not just divorce?
我试过了 她不肯
I've tried.
她认为我是想要她从真人秀获得的钱
She won't do it; she thinks I'll make a play
for her reality money.
好吧 关于她的威胁 她到底说了什么
Okay, her threat-- what did she say, exactly?
她告诉我 她会在我睡觉的时候割掉我的
She told me that she would chop off my, um... manhood...
男子气概 然后笑着看我流血致死
...while I slept, and then laugh as I bled to death.
呃 老天啊
Mm. Oh, my God.
我非常的爱他 他是我的整个世界
I love him so much. He's my whole world.
他怎么能用这样的事情来指责我
How can he accuse me of something like this?
-也许 -我真的不能理解
Well, maybe...I just don't understand.
这完全说不通啊
It doesn't make any sense!
Sheba 你可以别演了
Sheba.
You can stop now.
我们知道你的婚姻已经分崩离析了
We know your marriage is falling apart.
Todd告诉你的 对吧
[sighs] Todd told you that, huh?
符合他的作风
Typical.
那你为什么要让我这样哭哭啼啼的
Then why'd you let me go on blubbering like that?
你毁了我的睫毛膏了
You ruined my mascara.
我真的很抱歉
I am so sorry.
你为什么要那样哭哭滴滴的呢
Why were you blubbering like that?
这就是我
Look, this is me.
如果你不喜欢 换个频道
If you don't like it, change the channel.
三天前 你是否威胁过
Three days ago, did you threaten...
说真的 你们有没有一个镜子之类的
Seriously, do you guys have a mirror or something?
你们当然有啦
Of course you do.
真有趣 McGee 永远不要和你的英雄见面
SLOANE: Fascinating.
Never meet your heroes, McGee.
我不能够理解 她在节目里行为不是这样的
McGEE: I don't get it. She doesn't act like this on the show.
关键词 演
Key word: "act."
是啊 但是她不是一位演员 真人秀
Yeah, but she's not an actor. Reality shows...
依然是脱离现实的
Detach from reality.
Sheba 够了 请坐下
Okay, Sheba, enough. Sit down.
我可以和其他人说话嘛
Can I talk to someone else?
另外一个探员叫什么来着 McGoo
What's that other agent's name, McGoo?
他在那里面 对吗
He's in there, right?
-真迷人 -McGoo
Charming.McGoo?
我说了 坐下
I said sit down.
好吧
Fine.
总而言之 这个才是你应该对着表演的摄像头
Anyways, that's the camera you should be playing to.
等等 你们把这一切都录下来了吗
Wait, you guys are recording this?
你觉得我的制片人能否接触到这段录像呢
Hey, do you think my producers can get access to this tape?
你是否威胁了你的丈夫
Did you or did you not threaten your husband?
我来给你省点时间吧
Let me save you a lot of time.
我不知道怎么造炸弹
I don't know how to make a bomb.
但是你知道谁会吗 我丈夫
But you know who does? My husband.
海军教过他 他知道我会检查邮件
The Navy taught him. He knows I check the mail.
也许他把炸弹寄给他自己是为了避免被怀疑
Maybe he addressed the bomb to himself to avoid suspicion.
你是否考虑过这个呢
Did you ever think of that?
她说得很有道理
She makes a good point.
她的丈夫是一个受过训练的杀手
Her husband's a trained killer,
而且他还告诉过Torres他想脱离这段婚姻
and he told Torres he wanted out of the marriage.
就是不能放弃她 是吗 McGoo
Just can't quit her, huh, McGoo?
[phones ringing, woman speaking indistinctly over P.A.]
[groans softly]
-该死的 -噢
Shoot. Oh.
我来帮你
I'll get that for you.
哦 我的天啊
Oh, my goodness.
你是否介意我直接靠着你呢
Do you mind if I just lean on you?
-当然不介意 随你需要 -谢谢
Sure, whatever you need.Oh, thank you.
噢 谢谢
Oh. Thank you.
今天真的是一团糟
It has been a mess today.
[both laugh]
我没吃饭 还不得不把车停在3个街区外
I didn't eat. Had to park three blocks away.
我花了15分钟才把这条裤子给穿上
It took me 15 minutes to put on these pants.
[both laugh]
-好啦 -感谢上帝
Okay.Oh, thank God.
-这个给你 -谢谢
Here you go.Thank you.
啊
[sighs]: Ah.
[sighs]
看看我们 都属于还能走的伤员
Look at us. The walking wounded.
[both laugh]
你怎么了
What happened to you?
工伤
On-the-job injury.
抱歉 你是做什么的
Sorry. What do you do?
政府工作
Government work.In D.C.?
在华盛顿 不会吧
No way.[both laugh]
你呢
How about you?
-中学老师 -哦
Middle school teacher.Ah.
我学生们认为这个很滑稽
Yeah. My students think this is hilarious.
所以发生了什么
So what happened?Oh, it involved
这个涉及到2杯冰镇果汁朗姆酒和一个跳水台
two piña coladas and a diving board.
[laughs]
当年上大学的时候 我还是很灵活的
I was more flexible in college.
嗨 我当时也很灵活
Hey. We all were.
Mallory
Mallory?
该我上场了
That is my cue.
-让我来帮你拿包 你好 -噢 谢谢
Let me get your bag for you. Hi.Oh, thank you.
[sighs]
所以 我们从摆好躯干
So we start with the torso.
然后加上手臂
Then we add the arms.
下一步 我们摆上腿
Next up, we have
[strains]: the legs.
[grunts]
最后 组成头部
And then we have the head.
你忘记了 呃 眼睛 鼻子和嘴
You forgot the, uh, the eyes, nose and mouth.
不 不 我没有
No, no, I didn't.
Nick 我很抱歉 在刽子手游戏里没有脸
I'm sorry, there's no face in hangman, Nick.
噢 哇哦 McGee已经告诉你了
Oh, wow. McGee already told you?
[elevator bell dings]
这个人不够朋友 我就说这些
The man is not your friend. I'll just leave it at that.
你把什么留在哪里了
You'll leave what at what?
也许我应该离开
Maybe I should just leave.
我请Torres探员下来帮我
I asked Agent Torres to come down here and help me
确认这些纹身 我以为其中部分纹身
identify some of these tats; I thought some of them
-也许和帮派有关系 -不 他们没有关系
might be gang-related.No, they're not.
是啊 我现在知道了
Yeah. I know that now.
至于死因 并没有什么惊喜
As for cause of death, no surprise there.
我准备将这个命名为 死亡邮件
I am calling this one "Mail-order death."
这是什么
GIBBS: What is this?
在其中一个受害者的大腿里发现的
Found this embedded in one of the victims' thighs.
我想 它也许是个计时器
I think it might be a timing mechanism.
-在高温里融化了 -是的
Melted in the heat.Right.
Gibbs 这个炸弹装药量非常足
This bomb packed quite a punch, Gibbs.
有人希望能确保炸死Nicholas上士
Someone wanted Petty Officer Nicholas very dead.
这里有另外一条 Sheba 没有灵魂 无趣 肤浅
Here's another one. Sheba is "soulless, vapid, shallow..."
丢脸 可耻 令人尴尬
"Disgraceful, shameful, embarrassing..."
我在有钱人身上看到的最糟糕的发型
McGEE: "The most ratchet hair I've seen on a rich person"?
我猜粉丝们都看穿了她的表演
I guess fans saw through her act.
电视观众也是非常有见识的
TV viewers can be pretty savvy.
Delilah和我是怎么错过这些细节的
Well, how did Delilah and I miss it?
-你错过了什么 -老大我们正在
You missed what?Well, boss, we're doing
对 R-WOW 论坛做一个深入的研究 查找嫌疑人
a deep dive into the R-WOW forums looking for suspects.
那个 R什么
The R-What?
战争主妇
Real Wives of War.
事实是 网络上很多人都讨厌Sheba
Turns out the Internet hates Sheba.
我和网络上的观点一致
I agree with the Internet.
-关于丈夫的信息呢 -作为嫌疑犯还是目标
What about the husband?As a suspect or target?
目标
Target.
你知道所有的海豹突击队员都会进行爆破训练
You know that all SEALs undergo demolitions training.
是的 McGee 还有全套心理评估 一个海豹突击队员不会干这个的
Yeah, and full psych evals, McGee. A SEAL did not do this.
我们只找到了4条针对丈夫的网上威胁
We found only four online threats against the husband.
都是在9个月前由同一个人发布的
All posted nine months ago
by the same person.
Sheba 值得一个比她好战的老公
"Sheba deserves a better man
更好的人 她老公应该
"than her warmongering husband, who needs to
死在战场上
die on the battlefield."
噢 我听到过比这个更糟糕的
Oh, I've heard way worse than that.
LLL
GIBBS: "LLL..."
LLLeonardo
"LLLeonardo"?
真实名字是 Leonard Finnik
Oh, real name is Leonard Finnik.
住在巴尔的摩 你需要我们去拜访他一下吗
Lives in Baltimore. You want us to pay him a visit?
噢 伙计们 任何人都可以在网上说任何话
Oh, come on, guys. Anybody can say anything on the Internet.
当Shakira发布女狼现身专辑时
I myself have posted major shade
我也发表过负面评价
on Shakira when she released She Wolf.
你还记得那张专辑吧 Gibbs
You remember the album, right, Gibbs?
我可没有碰到联邦探员来问我问题
I didn't have any federal agents asking me questions.
Torres 一路平安
You drive safe, Torres.
带着McGee一起去
Take McGee with you.
过来2个小时等会儿回去还要2个小时 图个什么呢
Two hours here and two hours home, and for what?
我们可以把每个疑点都检查一下
We got to turn every stone.[knocks]
行啦 哥们 你看过这个人的档案吗
Come on, man. You look at this guy's file?
这个人是普通先生
This guy's Mr. Normal.
看 他还有一个欢迎地垫
Look, he's got a welcome mat.
在疯狂炸弹人的历史上 没有哪个做炸弹的人会有欢迎地垫
No mad bomber in the history of mad bombers has a welcome mat.
你是怎么知道这点的
And you know this how?
所有人都知道
Everyone knows this.
[knocks]
Leonard 联邦探员
TORRES: Leonard? Federal agents.
我们进来了
We're coming in.
你看 这里没有炸弹客的氛围
See, no Unabomber vibe here.
不过 这个家伙的音乐品味确实很差
Eek. This guy does have bad taste in music, though.
呵呵 这话竟然出自一个讨厌Shakira的人之口
Yeah, says the man who hates Shakira.
我很喜欢Shakira 我爱Shakira
Hey, I love Shakira. I love Shakira.
只是发泄而已
Just venting.
厨房安全
Kitchen's clear.
所以你到底在网上写了她什么
So what'd you write her, exactly?
厕所安全
Bathroom's clear.
Tim 那是我和Shakira之间的事儿
Tim, that is between me and Shakira.
卧室安全
Bedroom is clear.
普通先生也就这样啊
Well, so much for Mr. Normal, huh?
我知道你在观察我 只要你需要我随时随地都在
"I know you've been watching me. I'm here whenever you want me.
我们应该永远在一起
We belong together forever."
哇哦 永远是一个很长的时间
TORRES: Wow. Forever is
a very long time.
Do you want to tell Delilah, or should I?
你想要亲自告诉Delilah 还是我来说
Ha. No, these are from our suspect, Leonard Finnik.
哈 不 这些都来自于我们的嫌疑犯 Leonard Finnik
He's been sending Sheba love letters for months.
他给Sheba寄情书已经持续了几个月了
And stuffed animals, too.
还有毛绒动物
I thought maybe this can help with your investigation.
我想这个也许能帮助你们调查
Wha-- you kept gifts from your stalker?
你竟然留着来自跟踪狂的礼物
Well, a fan's a fan.
粉丝嘛
I'm sure you've read some of the things they say about me online.
我相信你也看到网上他们对我的评价了
I take what I can get.
能得到的我就接受
Besides, you should read what Leonard
除此之外 你应该读下Leonard写的有关我
writes about my...
Give me an update.TORRES: Oh, McGee was
有什么新消息
噢 McGee 刚刚正在获取新信息呢
just getting it.
老大 Sheba拿来了一箱来自 Lonard Finnik的信件
Boss, Sheba brought in a box of letters
from Leonard Finnik.
He's got a bee in his bonnet for Petty Officer Nicholas.
他是从骨子里针对着 Nicholas上士的
Talks about how "the enemy must be vanquished,"
说到 敌人必须被制服
calls him the "villain SEAL."
称呼他为 恶棍海豹突击队员
And I've got another eight boxes in my trunk.
我另外还有8个箱在我卡车上
Heavy boxes.Oh, I got them.
-很沉的箱子 -哦 我来拿吧
Torres, handle it.
Torres 你去处理
Uh, probably a better idea, boss.
呃 这个主意更好 老大
You got a location?
你找到他位置了吗
No, not yet. Uh, Finnik has no record,
不 暂时还没 呃 Finnik没有犯罪记录
no car, no job.
没有车 没有工作
He have a cell phone?Yes, but...
-他有手机吗 -有的 但是
Yes, but what?BISHOP: Uh, yes.
-但是什么 -呃 没错
Normally, we would ping it,
一般来说 我们会定位他的手机
but that meeting you missed this morning?
但是今早你没去的那个会议出了通告
No more pinging.[elevator bell dings]
不准乱定位了
Find some other way to get ahold of Leonard.
另想办法找到Leonard
Sure. I'll just use black magic.
好吧 我就用点黑魔法好了
[groans]
Oh, come on, this could be so easy.
哦 别这样 这本来很简单的
I'll just ping this one time and then never again.
我就用这一次定位 以后再也不用了
What about "privacy outweighs security"?
不是你说 隐私重于安全吗
There are no atheists in foxholes.Oh.
-紧急情况下没人会那么坚持原则 -哦
Vance never would've signed off on this.
Vance永远不会签署这种文件
Well, when he comes back, you should talk to him.
那等他回来了 你得跟他谈谈
If he gets back, you mean.
你应该说 如果他回来的话
Do you know something I don't?
你知道什么我不知道的事吗
All I know is that reentry is a bitch.
我只知道每次出远门游玩之后都不想回家
Yeah, I just finished.
是啊 我刚做完
KAYLA: How'd it go?Uh, it went well.
-做得怎样 -哦 挺不错的
You're headed to work now, right?
你现在准备去上班了 是吧
No, no. I'm way too sore to go to work. Uh...
不 没有 我腿太疼了 不能上班 呃
Dad, you promised.
老爸 你保证过的
Kayla, we're not gonna go through this again, okay?
Kayla 我们别再说这个了 好吗
Whatever. Bye.I told you, we...
-随便你 再见 -我说过的 我们...
Hello?
喂
Just tell her pain is progress.
就跟她说 腿疼也是进步了
Hey, there. Um, Mallory, right?
嗨 你好 呃 Mallory 对吧
Good memory. How'd your appointment go, uh...
记忆力真好 你的预约如何了
Leon. Um...
-Leon -呃
Ava beat me up pretty good, but nothing I can't handle.
Ava完全把我打败了 但是没什么我处理不了的
Oh, I'm sure you'll be running marathons in no time.
哦 我敢说你很快就能跑马拉松了
[both laugh]
Maybe half-marathons.
也许只能跑跑半马吧 你也来一起啊
How are you?I'll be cheering you on from the sidelines.
我会在路边给你加油
Still a long road ahead for me.
不过还得过好一阵才行
Hmm.AVA: Okay, Leon.
-嗯 -好的 Leon
Nice working with you.
跟你合作非常愉快
Um, you, too, uh, Ava.
呃 我也很愉快 Ava
What, are you, are you leaving?
怎么 你要离开吗
No, you are.
不 是你要离开了
They didn't tell you?No.
-他们没告诉你吗 -没有
You graduated. No more PT for you.
你毕业了 你不再需要理疗了
Wow. Congratulations.
哇哦 恭喜
Well, thanks.
谢谢
Um, I like your confidence, but I, um,
呃 感谢你对我这么有信心 但是 我 呃
still have a little hitch in my get along here.
身上还有点小问题
Some residual pain is normal.
出现阵痛很正常
But it shouldn't stop you getting back to your routine.
但你不应该被疼痛影响到自己的日程
You're cleared for work, too.Huh. Uh...
-你完全可以去工作了 -哈 呃
Yeah. Because, uh...
好吧 因为 呃
because I-I really, I-I really feel like I could use
因为 我 真的需要
another-another week of PT.
再接受一周的理疗
Well, if you need it, you need it.
如果你觉得有必要 那就再来一周吧
Okay.
好的
All right. Same time tomorrow?
好的 明天还是这个时间吧
All right.
好的
Every time I think I'm out, they pull me back in.
每次我觉得我能走了 他们就非得把我拖回来
Kase?Gibbs, you're just in time.
-Kase -Gibbs 你来得正是时候
Open the box.
打开盒子
What's in it?
里面是啥
A bomb.
炸弹
Just open it.
打开就是了
My first bomb. Neat, huh?
这是我第一颗炸弹 好看吧
[electrical whirring]
[sound effect crackles, pops, whistles]
Boom. [laughs]
嘭
I built a replica
我根据
based on the components I found among the fragments.
碎片里面找到的各个组件 做了一个复制品
There's the power source
那是电源
and the trigger mechanism.Photo cell.
-这是触发装置 -光敏开关
Rigged to explode when it detects light.
光一照就炸
Two caps, two fire-sets.
两个引爆器 两种引爆方式
Redundancies to ensure detonation.
确保一定能炸
This guy knew what he was doing.
这个伙计知道他在做什么
This guy?
这个伙计
Well, I assume all bombers are dudes.
我一般假设所有炸弹客都是哥们儿
Right. Never assume.
对哈 绝不假设
Yeah. And never say "dudes."
没错 而且永远别说 哥们儿
What else you got?
你还查到什么了
I analyzed this object
我分析了Jimmy发现的这个
Jimmy found embedded in our victim's leg.
嵌入到受害者大腿的东西
Metal alloy plated with 22-karat gold.
是镀有22K金的合金材料
It came from our bomb, but I can't
它来自我们的炸弹 但是我没法
figure out its function.
确定它是用来干啥的
Ooh, and look at the back.
哦 看看后边
See how it's raised?
看到这个突起了吗
Maybe that part came from a clasp or a pin.
这可能是某种扣环或者图钉
Call me crazy, but this looks like a brooch.
你可能觉得我疯了 但这看起来像个胸针
Oh, you're not exactly a brooch guy. [chuckles]
哦 你不是那种带胸针的人
It's, um, it's a piece of jewelry,
那是 呃 一种饰品
like a clip, that you wear on your lapel.
就像你西服上的那个别针
Like a fancy, older lady might.
就是年长女士喜欢的那种
You know, it's probably not a brooch at all.
得了 这可能根本不是什么胸针
I should probably just keep working. Toodle-oo.
我大概还是继续干活吧 再见
[chuckles]
McGEE: First, I had to track
首先 我跟踪
Leonard's credit card to the stationery store.
Leonard的信用卡信息 到了一个文具店
Right? Then I had to go through the store's
好吧 然后我调阅了商店停车场的
parking lot surveillance security footage
监控录像
to find the car he drove-- his mom's, by the way.
找到他开的车 顺便说一句 那车是他妈的
Then I had to sift through red light cameras
然后我把红绿灯监控筛查了一遍
to track him to this barber shop.
才查出他来了这个理发店
It's called work, brah.
这就是工作啊 兄逮
It's unnecessary work.
这些活本来不用干的
I could've just pinged him.
我只要给定位他就可以了
Rules are rules, Mr. Hangman.
规定就是规定啊 刽子手专家
Look, hey, just bec...McGee.
-听着 嗨 不能就因... -McGee
What's he carrying?
他拿的是什么
Leonard.Yes?
-Leonard -怎么
Federal agents.
联邦探员
Drop the box.
放下盒子
McGEE: Wait, no.
等等 别
Don't drop the box.
别放下盒子
Right. Don't-don't drop the box.
对哦 别放盒子
Excuse me, everyone, federal agents.
抱歉 各位 我们是联邦探员
Please calmly and quickly clear the area.
请保持镇定尽快离开这里
No, not you, Leonard.
不 你别跑 Leonard
You get back here. Don't move.
你得回来 别动
Bishop, bomb squad, Lemon and Fifth.
Bishop，叫拆弹小组来，Lemon&Fifth理发店
Bomb squad?
拆弹小组
Wait, for this?
等等 就为这个吗
Wait, wait, wait, wait. Stop, stop!Don't! Get down!
-等等 等等 别动 别 -别 快趴下
Huh.
哈
That's the Little Bighorn River,
这是Little Bighorn河
and that's a pronghorn deer,
那是叉角鹿
and an otter and, uh,
还有一只水獭 还有 呃
that's me and, uh...
那是我 和 呃
Sheba and your love child.
Sheba还有你们可爱的孩子
Yeah, we've been over this.
好了 你已经说过这些了
Leonard.
Leonard
I need to talk to you about your bedroom.
我得跟你谈谈你卧室的问题
This is the hollowed-out log for fishing or, you know...
这个中空的原木用来钓鱼 或者...
Leonard. Focus.
Leonard 专注点
Bedroom.
卧室
Oh, do you like it? Sheba loves it.
哦 你喜欢吗 Sheba很喜欢
You talked to her? Yeah.
-你跟她聊过吗 -对啊
She told me in a dream the other night.
前两天她在梦里告诉我的
No, she didn't.
不 她没有
Uh, were you there?
呃 你在我梦里吗
Dreams are not reality, Leonard.
梦又不是真的 Leonard
You are so naive.
你太天真了
Okay. All right, explain this to me.
好吧 那你跟我解释一下
So this is you?
那么这是你吗
LEONARD: Right. Yeah, yeah.
没错 是的
That's Sheba.
那是Sheba
LEONARD: Uh-huh. Pretty hair.
没错 头发很漂亮
And that is a dead buffalo.
这是一个死去的水牛
LEONARD: Correct. That's correct.
没错 完全正确
Who is the dead buffalo?
谁是这个死去的水牛呢
Is that Sheba's husband, Petty Officer Nicholas?
是不是Sheba的丈夫 Nicholas上士呢
Leonard.
Leonard
Did Sheba ask you to kill her husband in that dream?
Sheba在那个梦里有没有让你杀掉她的丈夫呢
Episode 33,
第33集
just after the commercial about the tortilla chips,
就在玉米片的商业广告之后
Sheba's white shirt isn't ironed.
Sheba的白衬衫没有熨平
And she just gives me the littlest nod, like so.
她对我轻轻地点了个头 就像这样
She goes...
她这样
Wow.
哇哦
Yeah.
没错
What does that mean?
那是什么意思呢
It means nothing.
那什么意思也不是
You don't think he's our guy?
你觉得他不是我们要找的人吗
His cord doesn't quite reach the outlet,
他的心智很不正常
but I've read his file
但我读过他的档案
and he has never shown a propensity towards violence
他从没表现出过暴力倾向
and I doubt he would start now.
我觉得他不会突然就变了
So, should we go rescue Torres?
所以 我们要把Torres救出来吗
We got a problem.
我们有麻烦了
Another mail bomb just detonated.
另一个邮件炸弹刚爆炸了
What? Where?
什么 在哪
Alexandria. One dead.
在Alexandria 一人死亡
Same M.O. as the first bomb
跟第一个炸弹有同样的作案手法
and this one came by one-hour delivery.
这一个是用一小时快递寄过去的
Leonard在这里待了俩小时了
Leonard's been in here for two.
Yeah, which means...
没错 也就是说
我们还有一个多重炸弹客在外边游荡
We've got a serial bomber on the loose.
两次炸弹袭击 三个受害者 还会有更多吗
Two bombs, three victims. Will there be more?
今天 这个问题让城市几近瘫痪
That's the question paralyzing the city today
NCIS作为这次调查的牵头机构
as pressure mounts on NCIS, which has taken the lead
压力逐渐增加 即便是部门主任
in the investigation, even as the agency's director
仍在接受治...
remains on extended medic...
我们不生产新闻 有什么进展
We don't make news. Update.
第二个炸弹的受害人是Patricia Everett
McGEE: Second bombing victim was Patricia Everett.
48岁 离异 两个孩子在上大学
48 years old, divorced, two kids in college.
邮件通过Global Courier公司的
Package was delivered via Global Courier's
一小时快递服务送达
one-hour delivery service.
Everett才是收件人
Everett was the recipient.
-寄件人是谁 -用的假名字 跟上一个一样
Who's the sender?Fake. Just like the last one.
-两个目标有甚么联系 -暂时没查到
GIBBS: What's the connection with our targets?BISHOP: Nothing yet.
呃 没有共同的朋友 社交媒体上也没有交集
Uh, no mutual friends, no social media overlap
我们查过的六度分离范围内也没有交集
【注:六度分离意为世界上任何两人之间可以最多通过六个人就能够联系起来】
and no six degrees of Kevin Bacon and we've looked.
继续找
Look harder.
如果他们之间没有联系呢
What if there is no connection?
如果炸弹客就是从电话本上随便找目标呢
What if the bomber is picking his targets from the phone book?
嘿 Gibbs
"Hey, Gibbs.
我们得谈谈
"Need to talk...
第二个炸弹的事儿
about second bomb."
不 等等 他又不看短信
Oh, wait. Oh, not a texter.
啊
Ah.
我犯蠢了
Stupid.
-有什么收获 -啊
What we got? Oh.
你要是想的话 可以再放一次
We can do this again if you'd like.
不 不好意思
No, um, sorry. [chuckles]
我进行了化学分析
Uh, so I ran a chemical analysis
可以确认这两个炸弹
and was able to confirm both bombs
出自于同一人之手
were built by the same person.
他们包含着完全一致的
Both contained identical isomers
硝化纤维 三硝基苯
of nitrocellulose, trinitrobenzene
以及过氧化丙酮的异构体
and acetone peroxide.
TNB吗 那是军队惯用的
TNB? That's military ordinance.
是这样没错 还有
Oh, yes, indeed. Oh, also,
我发现了第二个胸针
I found a second brooch,
-如果你还记得 胸针是... - 嗯 对 我记得
which, if you recall, a brooch is a...Yeah. Yeah, yeah, I recall.
还有 我没发现这个胸针对于炸弹
Again, I can find no function that this serves
有什么作用
in the bomb.
那是炸弹制作者的签名
It's the bomber's signature.
好吧 那么 他想用它说明什么呢
Okay, yeah, well, what's he trying to say with it?
Budweiser
【三叉戟别针：为完成海豹突击队训练并被指定为海豹突击队员所有】
Budweiser.
Budweiser
【三叉戟别针：为完成海豹突击队训练并被指定为海豹突击队员所有】
Budweiser?
谢谢
Thank you.
到底发生什么了
What happened exactly?
Kasie Hines，等等
Kasie Hines, no, no.
你留在这里
You stay here.
马上就会找出真相了
You're gonna find out what happened soon enough.
Budweiser领针
TORRES: The Budweiser.
这个让人垂涎三尺的三叉戟
The coveted trident pin
会在毕业典礼上发给所有的海豹突击队员
awarded to all Navy SEALs upon graduation.
你觉得那是一个融化了的三叉戟
BISHOP: And you think that's a melted trident?
炸弹与海豹队员有关
The bombs are SEAL related.
但我们已经查过了
But we've been over this.
Pat Everett与海军没有关系
Pat Everett has no connection to the Navy.
我们已经查过了与Nicholas士官
And we vetted all 20 Navy SEALs
同期毕业的20个海豹突击队员
that were in Petty Officer Nicholas's graduating class.
那么没撑到毕业的那些人呢
What about the ones who rang out?
那名单可长了 稍等
It's a bigger list. Hold on.
呃
Um...
有204个候选者被淘汰
204 candidates washed out.
其中有多少通过了爆破训练
How many made it through demolition training?
这个可以缩小范围
That should narrow it down.
只有16个
Only 16.
这16人里有多少没通过心理评估
How many of those 16 failed their psych eval?
只有一个
Only one.
放出来
Put him up.
嗯  David West
Hmm. David West.
四个月前他被淘汰了
He washed out about four months ago.
现在他住在西弗吉尼亚 在一个商场当保安
Now lives in West Virginia where he works security at a mall.
看看这个
McGEE: Look at that.
负责West心理评估的心理专家
The psychologist that administered West's psych eval
是Patrick Everett医生
was a Dr. Patrick Everett.
是不是有点眼熟
Sound familiar?
第二个炸弹的受害者就叫Patricia Everett
The second bomb victim was Patricia Everett.
这肯定不是巧合
Can't be a coincidence.
要么我们的投弹者非常痛恨Everett一家
Either our bomber really hates the Everett family...
现在还不清楚他们的关系
Don't know if they're related.
要么他杀错了这个Pat Everett
...or he killed the wrong Pat Everett.
现在West在哪
Where is West right now?
定位他的电话
Pinging his cell phone.
Boss 我就想说我觉得
Boss, let me just say that I think
这个新的禁止定位条例糟糕透了
this new nonpinging policy sucks.
McGee, we got the mall.
McGee 我们负责商场
Bishop、Torres，去他家里
Bishop, Torres, take his house.
走吧
Let's go.
嗨
Hi.
你怎么样 Kayle
How are you, Kayla?
噢 我 我是打给Gibbs的
Oh. I-I called Gibbs.
然后他打给了我 你爸爸怎么样了
And he called me. How's your dad?
不太好
Not great.
他好像失去了魔力或者别的什么
It's like he's lost his mojo or something.
那我们会帮他找回来
Well, we'll have to help him get it back. Yeah.
好的
Jack
Jack?
-嗨 Leon 你近况如何 -还行
Hey, Leon. How you doing?Hey. Okay.
-见到你真好 -我也是
Good to see you. You, too.
哇哦
You, too. Oh. [laughs]
-很能干嘛  -噢 这个啊
Handy. Oh, shoot.
正在做个房屋装修
Home improvement project.
我客房的窗户有些问题
I got a sticky window in the guest room.
不过在这屋子里 有些问题是解决不了的
Something else in this house won't budge.
我们这次见面又是谁的主意
And to what do we owe this visit?
正好经过这里 想看看你在做什么
Was just in the area, wanted to see how you're doing.
我一天比一天好
I'm better every day.
很期待我能够回到办公室
I'm looking forward to getting back into the office.
嗯嗯
Mm-hmm.
你根本不是"正在这里" 是吧？
You weren't "in the area," were you?
你也不是"一天比一天好" 不对吗
And you're not "better every day," are you?
我是不是该感谢你这么多事
And I have you to thank for this?
有人要来点咖啡吗 我想要
Who wants coffee? I do.
谢谢
Thank you.
那么 都告诉我吧 出什么事了
So, tell me everything. What's happening?
行啊 我们干嘛不省掉所有的客套
Yeah, why don't we skip all the pleasantries
告诉我你来这里的真实目的
and you can tell me why you're really here?
好吧 想要我赶快撕开你遮掩伤口的创可贴
Okay. Want to just rip that Band-Aid off fast?
我是没意见
Fine with me.
你被一个恐怖分子欺骗 Leon
You were tricked by a terrorist, Leon.
你曾做出一个坏的决断 差点断送数以千计的生命
You made a bad decision that nearly cost thousands of lives
现在你面对这个过错的方法
and now you are coping with that mistake
是尝试回避以及社会退缩
by practicing avoidance and social withdrawal.
怎么样
How about that?
我正在治疗我的胯骨
[chuckles] I am rehabbing my hip.
就这些
That's all.
这叫推卸责任 另外 在你这样的状态下
That's blame shifting. Normal defense mechanism
这是正常的防御机制
for someone in your condition, by the way.
Jack 我没事
Jack, I'm fine.
不 你很害怕
No, you're afraid.
你不再相信自己的直觉
You don't trust your instincts anymore.
对于一个
Not good for someone
每天都在做生死抉择的人来说这不是好事
who makes life or death decisions every day
恐惧会麻痹自己 Leon
and that fear can be paralyzing, Leon.
我一直以为 心理学家
I always thought that psychologists
会先检查他们的病人
would examine their patients
再提供诊断
before providing diagnosis.
不 我们没有那么多时间
Ah, no, we don't have time for that,
所以我直接说结论
so I just thought I'd skip to the end.
那么我很确定你恰好有正确的处方
And I'm sure you have just the right prescription.
事实上 我确实有
As a matter of fact, I do.
出于我专业的观点
In my professional opinion...
你得把你的屁股挪回正确的马鞍上去
you need to get your ass back in the saddle.
感谢你过来 Jack
Thanks for stopping by, Jack.
Leon 听着
Leon, listen.
嘿 你想真正解决那个
Hey. You want a real project
摆在你屋里的问题吗
to do around the house?
你所领导的部门
The agency that you lead
正试图阻止一个连环炸弹凶犯
is trying to stop a serial bomber.
这是关于嫌犯你需要知道的所有资料
Everything you need to know about the suspect.
David West吗
David West?
等等 海军罪案调查处
TORRES: Wait. NCIS!
West先生 我们只是来问几个问题
Mr. West, we just have a few questions!
冷静 冷静
Easy, easy, easy.
有枪
Gun!
好吧 我觉得他不想和我们说话
Okay. I don't think he wants to talk to us.
他可以和我的爱枪谈一谈
He can talk to my SIG.
-准备好了 1... -嗯
Ready? One... Yeah.
-2... -Nick
...two... Nick.
跑 快跑
Go. Go!
跑
Go!
好的 特警队正在路上
Okay. SWAT team's on the way.
Gibbs and McGee are coming back from the mall.
Gibbs和McGee正从那商场回来
They should be here any minute. All right?All right.
-他们随时可能过来 好吗 -好的
现在 让我来瞧瞧这个
Now, let me take a look at this.
[groans] Ow, ow.
哇哦
Ooh...
哇
有多严重
How bad is it?
Uh, it's not great, Nick. Ooh.
呃 不太好 Nick
Oh, Bishop!Shrapnel's in there pretty deep.
-哇 Bishop -弹片有点儿深
噢 这可真好
Oh, that's peachy.
好吧
Okay.
Cut it out.
把它弄出来
You're not serious.
你不是认真的吧
是啊 我很认真 把它弄出来
Yes, I'm serious. Cut it out.
-不行 Nick -这个人想杀了我 好吗
No, Nick. This guy tried to kill me, okay?
I'm about to try to kill him,
我要去干掉他
but I can't do it with that thing in my back,
但是这东西在我背上我没法做到
-只要 只要挖出来就行 -好吧
so just-just dig it out. Okay.
Fine. You're an idiot.
好吧 你真是白痴
等等 那又是干什么
Wait, what's that for?
I'm sterilizing my tool. Here.
我在给工具消毒 这个
咬住这个
Bite onto this.
喔 我们要弄这个吗
Oh. Oh, we're doing this.
你还没下定决心吗
Can you make up your mind already?
Well, I'm just saying
呃 我只是在说
that maybe-maybe that guy is gone.
那个 那家伙可能已经跑了
我没听到他开枪了 大概吧
I-I didn't hear him shoot for, like, a little bit.
Oh, the guy is gone. Are you...
那家伙走了 你...
你在干嘛 你在干嘛啊
What are you doing? What are you doing?
他还在这儿
[gunshot]He's still there.
That was my favorite hat.
那是我最喜欢的帽子
Can... are we gonna do this or what?
你能...我们是不是得开始了
Okay, I'm ready. I'm ready, I'm ready. Okay.
-好吧 我准备好了 已经好了 -那行
-1 2...-嘿 Torres
One, two... McGEE: Hey, Torres.
等等 等等 等等
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait!
-游骑兵来了 -什么
The cavalry's here.What?
What is he doing?Uh, no idea.
-他在做什么 -呃 不知道
他去哪了
BISHOP: Where did he go?
Gibbs呢
Where's Gibbs?
[grunting]
Okay, I got him, boss.
可以了 让我来吧 头儿
Bishop和Torres怎么样了
Bishop and Torres?
Oh, they're okay.
他们没事
Bishop
Bishop!
Torres
Torres!
停火 我们要出来了
Cease fire, we're on the way out!
帽子不错
Nice hat.
在战争时代里 在动荡岁月中
In times of war and uncertainty,
有一位生来就与众不同的勇士
there is a special breed of
warrior ready to answer our nation's call.
为响应国家的号召而准备着
A common man with an uncommon desire to succeed...
一个普通人有着对胜利不寻常的渴望
Director Vance.Special Agent Gibbs.
-Vance主任 -Gibbs探员
很高兴见到你
Good to see you.
很高兴来到这里
Good to be here.
与众不同的勇士
...special breed of warrior
为响应国家的号召而准备着
ready to answer our nation's call.
海豹突击队的信条
The Navy SEAL creed.
他上个小时一直在背这个
He's been reciting it for the last hour.
他的生活一直是围绕着成为海豹队员
He built his whole life around becoming a SEAL.
当他失去资格后 便没有什么可依托的了
When he washed out, he had nothing to fall back on.
你读过了他的档案
You read his file.
看了三遍
Three times.
DAVID: My word is my bond.
我言出必行
我正好闲着没事
I've had some time on my hands.
接受领导 没有命令时
DAVID: ...and be led. In the absence of orders,
我将站出来负责
I will take charge,
lead my teammates and accomplish the mission.
领导我的队友完成任务
I lead by example in all situations.
在任何情况下 我都以身作则
我永不退缩 苦难只会使我坚持
I will never quit. I persevere and thrive
使我更加强大 我的祖国
on adversity. My nation
希望我
expects me to...
你认出来了吗
You recognize that?
你可能认不出 因为你从没有得到过
Maybe you don't, since you never earned one,
这是Budweiser三叉戟别针
but it's a Budweiser, trident pin.
这个是真的
It's a real one,
不是你在海军二手货店里买的
unlike the knockoffs you purchased
装进邮件炸弹里的山寨货
at the Navy surplus store and packed into your mail bombs.
Sorry. Budweisers are for SEALs only.
抱歉 Budweiser只有海豹突击队员才有资格有
而你没有资格
And you washed out.
Everett医生犯了个错误
Dr. Everett made a mistake,
长官
sir.
所以你就给他寄了个炸弹吗
So you sent him a bomb?
还给Nicholas军士寄了一个
Along with one to Petty Officer Nicholas,
就因为他没让你通过心理测试吗
who red-flagged you for a psych exam?
他们这是罪有应得 女士
They got what they deserved, ma'am.
不
No, they didn't.
Nicholas还活着 你错杀了另一个Everett
Nicholas is still alive, and you killed the wrong Everett.
任务失败了
Mission failed.
你赢了一些 也输了一些
You win some, you lose some.
他怎么这么自以为是
The hell is he so smug about?
你为什么不去找到答案呢
Why don't you go find out?
你读了他的档案
You read his file...
读了三遍
three times.
Vance 主任 欢迎回
Director Vance, welcome ba--
他要去哪里
Where's he going?
你过得开心吗
Are you having a good time?
长官
Sir?
你想告诉我什么事那么有趣吗
You want to tell me what's so funny?
我们接受训练是为了作战 我们参加战斗是为了获胜
We train for war and fight to win.
我时刻准备着将我全部的战斗能量发挥出来
I stand ready to bring the full spectrum of combat power
以完成我的任务
to bear in order to achieve
达成国家为我设定的目标
my mission and the goals established by my country.
你看了好几次手表
You've been looking at your watch a lot.
你要迟到了吗 David
Are you late for something, David?
执行任务时 只要形势需要
The execution of my abilities will be swift
我会迅猛而激烈
and violent when required...
或者是我迟了
Or am I?
我仍会受纪律的约束 因为这是我努力捍卫的东西
...the very principles that I serve to defend.
勇敢的人战斗过了 他们即便死去 也会树立起令人骄傲的传统
Brave men have fought and died building the proud tradition...
你寄出了第三个炸弹 是吗
You sent a third bomb, didn't you?
第三个目标是谁
Who is the third target?
是谁
Who is it?
还有谁愧对你了
Who else wronged you?
会是另一个海豹突击队的同学吗
Could it have been another SEAL classmate?
他们里面20个都毕业了
20 of them graduated.
去查吧
Yeah, go.
晒过的痕迹很好看
That's a nice tan line.
戒指去哪了
Where's the ring?
David 你刚结婚 你的婚戒在哪里
David, you just got married. Where's your wedding band?
谢谢
WOMAN: Thanks.
目标是他妻子
It's the wife.
Gwen Eisley 五个月前结的婚
Gwen Eisley. Married five months ago.
她抛弃了你 对吧
She walked out on you, huh?
她住在哪里
Where's she staying?
在Alexandria的娘家吗
She at her mother's house in Alexandria?
或者住在Philly的弟弟家
Or maybe she's staying at her brother's in Philly?
还是在Middleburg的姐姐家
Or she's staying at her sister's in Middleburg?
在Middleburg她姐姐家
Sister's in Middleburg.
在监狱里别板着一张脸
Don't play poker in prison, David.
你有得是故事可讲
You have a tell.
[phone ringing]
留个言就行
Leave a message.
[phone ringing]
[scoffs]
什么
What?
他太太终于接了电话吗
So the wife finally answered her cell?
打了五次终于有效果了
Fifth time's a charm.
她老公给她寄了枚炸弹
How'd she react to the news
她对此有何反应
her hubby mailed her a bomb?
她问我能不能退还给寄件人
She asked if she could "return to sender."
McGee 快看
Ah, McGee, look.
今晚的战争主妇
ANNOUNCER: ...and coming up tonight on Real Wives of War,
Sheba散发着红色光芒
Sheba radiates in red.
天堂陷阱吗
【刘别谦1932年所导的电影】
Oh, whoa. Trouble in paradise?
我已经不看真实主妇之战这个节目了
You know what? I think I'm done with The Real Wives of War.
好样的
Good for you. Yeah.
你可以做些更好的事情
You can do better things with your life.
完全同意
Totally agree.
有个新节目 是关于迈阿密海滩的警察
There's this new show about cops in Miami Beach...
[groans]
McGee
McGee.
你不感兴趣吗
Not where you were going with that?
-好的 -他回来了
Okay.TORRES: He's back, baby.
-嘿 -不能让我失望
Hey. Can't keep me down.
手术怎么样
How was surgery?
轻而易举
Oh, it was a breeze.
弹片都被取出来了
Shrapnel's all out.
说了这只是个新伤口
Told you it was just a flesh would.
我本来可以切开的
Ah. So I could've cut it out.
不要 那个主意真是太糟糕了
Oh, no, that was a real bad idea.
我就是这么说的
Yeah, that's what I said.
只要30秒
30 seconds.
你们会很开心的 我保证
You'll be happy, I promise.
-表示怀疑 -一个词 定位
Doubt it.One word: ping.
你把他的超能力拿走了
You took away his superpower.
因为你没让我结束我的报告
Because you didn't let me finish my presentation.
的确 最高法院
Yes, the Supreme Court
禁止了没有逮捕令的手机定位追踪
banned warrantless cell location tracking...
也就是说 不能定位
AKA no ping.
这就是我们安排了三位随叫随到的法官
...which is why we have arranged for three on-call judges
能立刻提供所需要的逮捕令
to provide near-instantaneous warrants should the need arise.
-哼 -那是什么意思
Hm. Wait, what does that mean?
意思是我们能重新干活了 孩子们
Means we are back in business, baby.
不用谢
You're welcome.
她人真好
She's very sweet.
-是啊 -是啊
Yeah. Very.
她那么好
Yeah, when she's nice like that, yeah.
行 Cameron 周四见
Okay, Cameron, I'll see you Thursday.
Leon你可以改天再来
Hey, Leon, you can change in back.
事实上 Ava 我
Oh, uh, actually, Ava, I'm not
今天不是来接受治疗的
taking therapy today,
以后也不了 我取消了我的预约
or ever, I'm, uh, I'm canceling my appointments.
取消了你自己要的预约吗
Cancel the appointments you demanded?
是被要求的预约
Requested.
你是对的 我的活动机能很好
But you were right, my range of motion's good,
我在家也可以继续锻炼
and I can continue the exercises at home.
好的 我会取消的
Okay, I'll cancel them.
你打个电话就行的
You know, you could've just called.
我之前在这附近
I was in the neighborhood.
我想她现在还不在这里
Uh-huh. I don't think she's here yet.
谁
Who?
[chuckles]
很好 很好 很好
Well, well, well.
Leon
Leon.
拆掉固定板了吗
But no, uh, no more cast.
没有了 只需要拐杖了 你呢
Nope, just the crutches now. What about you?
我没觉得你走路蹒跚
I barely notice a limp.
我痊愈了 不需要理疗了
I graduated. No more PT.
-恭喜你 -谢谢
Oh, congratulations.Thank you.
祝你好运
Well, good luck with your life, I guess.
嘿 呃
Hey, um...
你...
How would you...
你愿不愿意和我见一面
How would you like to, um, see each other,
不是在这里 别的地方
somewhere that's not here?
-我很乐意 -好极了
I'd like that. Great.
滑水 登山 你喜欢吗
Waterskiing, mountain climbing, what do you think?
[both laugh]
或者 今晚一起吃晚餐
Or we could just do dinner tonight.
晚餐听起来不错 把你手机给我
Dinner sounds good. Give me your phone.
为什么要我的手机
My phone? Why?
-那样我就可以把我的电话号码输进去了 -喔 是啊
So I can put my number in it.Oh, geez.
我在这方面有些迟钝
I'm a little... little rusty here.
那么 对晚餐有什么要求吗
So any, um, any requests for dinner?
不需要走楼梯的地方怎么样
How about someplace without stairs?
我明白了 平地餐厅
Duly noted. Ground-floor restaurant.
好了
All right.
-我会 打电话给你的 -好的
I'll-I'll call you.Okay.
-再见 -再见
Bye. Bye.
干得不错
Nice work.
谢谢你
Thank you.
你的评价是什么
What's your assessment?
我还不知道 但我会知道的
I don't know yet, but I will.
嗯
Hm.
做得好
Well done.
我们要监视他多久
How long are we surveilling him?
不论多久 有收获就行
As long as it takes.
晚餐愉快
Enjoy your dinner.
[both chuckle]
嘿
Hey.
你忘了样东西
You forgetting something?
今晚你可不想要犯错
You don't want to make that mistake tonight.
你做好自己的事情吧 我的事情我自己来操心
You worry about you. I'll worry about me.
Captioning sponsored by CBS
Captioned by Media Access Group at WGBH access.wgbh.org